My question was that I have 500 shares of ICIC JR Insurance
at ₹178.
Ok.
So, Somnath ji, you are asking for a long term.   It is
not mine.  Ultimately three months
means till December 2025.
Ok.  You will want it till December.   To
take profit in this.  But
Somnath ji is running at a slight loss.  There is a loss of around ₹74 per share.
1978 Their purchase
is working at the level of 1903.  Ah,
however, if you see,
Manas ji, it has given a return of 10% more in the last 6 months
and its 52 week high is 2301.
Where are you looking at the 2000 levels?  Till when will
ICICI LB show the level of 2000 again
and what should they do?  Want to hold onto this until December
?  So, it is too
early to say that any positive move
is expected here because
if you see,
lower tops and lower bottoms are still being formed on the daily chart.  The only
positive sign is that the stock has regained its 200-
day moving average.
So a bottom has formed around ₹1800.  So
if you want to hold the position then
hold the position by placing a stop loss of ₹1800.  See, the place is right from where the
reversal can be seen.  But only
a confirmation is awaited.  So you
hold the position with a stop loss of 1800.  If 1940
crosses above 1940 then
you will get to see targets till 2060.